Hello friends, you are heartily welcome to the India YouTube channel.
You are watching the
Stock India YouTube channel. We could
not watch it because the market was waiting for today's
things and if we look at those
things, then today it
started from
there and the market was seen there, so we will
see the previous ones, let's
talk about
some of the stocks today. The latest updates are being seen on the channel, so
their discussion, the
main discussion related to today's stock, will be done
in this video, let's
see the news of the latest updates, the
LNT group has seen the
bullet train from Mumbai to Ahmedabad, which is a
very big project for the bullet train project, see, the
Mumbai to Ahmedabad bullet train is going to start
and this project of it, so
today a video on this from the LNT group, the
bullet train project which will run between Mumbai and Ahmedabad,
its project is spread in the
middle of Gujarat and the project in Gujarat is
spread
according to the project classification
of the company, big project files in the
range 250 crores
5000 crores, that is, this will be in
between the projects and this big project is being
seen going into the lap of the available  So
look at this project, the
L&T group announced on Monday that the
big daughter-in-law of the
Mumbai to Ahmedabad bullet train
project is proposed. This is a project with a
budget of around Rs 5 crore
and the company has issued a company statement
alert that the final range of
this project is between Rs 2500 crore to Rs 504 crore.
This is a big news on L&T from the project side. So let's
see if you have LTD on this tomorrow. The
second rule is Jindal Steel. Jindal
Steel has
a partnership with Renewable Energy Power Limited and this
partnership is in the renewable energy
sector and
Jindal Steel
Power Limited is also having contact with renewable energy power project.
This project is around 100
units per
year and the
project is a wheel generator
room and remote
project which is
also time
protective and the project is about
700 million units of energy generation.  But why year
because and this solar and wind technology
focus loan, from here in our
loan segment, not in banks, it has been
said in its statement that our
state loan book will be for
Assamese enterprises, their
lending and supply chain finance for the
Future Group, that is, the center for the loan for feature growth, they will
make the assembly and that is, you can also make your
statement swift focus on such me i.e. small
and medium
enterprises and supply chain finance for
the Future Group, that is, the work of giving loans to small and medium will be
focused so that there will be a lot of focus on the finance of the loans, so that there is a
need to
increase the partnership with the index company and there is engagement with them, it will be
9%, it is planned to Future Accelerator
problem, the second half of the current fee is
not clear and the company is planning to expand
its business due to its partnership with the digital companies, to
expand its business, its
network is
3.5 billion customers and 35%
20%
Credit card with Amazon and
its customer base is 30.5 billion and
35% of it is
35% and 20% has become high, I
will tell you that its customers have partnered with a printer company, the
partnership can be quite big, it is going to
focus a lot on small and medium enterprises,
beauty tips to
Assamese Assamese means small and medium
enterprises, the work of
giving loans to small and medium sized industries, now the focus will be on them,
in the future it is going to increase a lot, don't
full to D management,
that 30%
quality Hindi supply chain segment is in
strong momentum in new client
addition cross corporates and vendors, that is, because of the strategy made by these
guys to focus on two channels, the growth of the bank is
30% and holding up
quality supply, due to which there will be loan in the segment and supply
change, that is going to be
strong in the piece, so ICICI
Bank can maintain a lot of focus, it will be
in a position to do much better
because right now there will be a lot of focus on these
So if we look at digital payments, we will find that
India's digital transactions can
increase up to 38 lakh crores and it is
around 23 billion, so
see, digital transactions include payments
by the Unified Payment in UPI, all the
payments that are happening and
till the third quarter of this quarter, there are 19 billion
transactions in your volume and transactions worth 35.5 lakh
crores have been done,
which is going to be
23.06 billion digital transactions for the economy,
38.3 lakh
23, the
third quarter of that will be
in a report, there is such a report
23, till the third quarter of that,
India's digital transactions in India
and its value will be around 38 lakh crores, so
in terms of digital transactions, India is
quite big in India,
so the loans of the companies that can be kept through digital transactions committee are quite
big in India and this has been said in a report,
a report has come out.
13.5% from FY 212,
FY 22 and 8% from June 21, the two
wheeler loan here is
13% in 2022, group has been given in it, so friends, let's talk about a
good
business recording
student, that is, Sweden's
Koshish
Center, that is, the Kanhaiya Center, for
all the services of Infosys, it has established
Sweden Wooden Bracket, Sweden
's Gutenberg
New Production,
a global leader in the next generation
digital service and consulting center,
loading next generation, if you
see,
what is this concentration established, its purpose is that
Infosys will
invest in the countries of the regions and the people of Infosys will be able to
make their own centers according to the location and in the areas where it has
its services, such as next
generation digital services,
from a position to provide better services to the clients and
this center has been established there, so for tomorrow
you can keep a discussion on this also on Infosys  Yes,
and this is not Infosys,
it has set up a large central staff in Sweden, with the
help of which it will be in a much better position to
provide its services in Sweden and its areas.
[Music] The
hydropower development of
ICICI
Group, its renewable cycle will
increase and include operation of solar
hybrid capacity of 1.4 covering location
450 megawatts. The World Cup Winner 2016 has been installed,
due to which the power generation
capacity of this green company has increased significantly and
it has increased to about 7.15 news
and
one minute with the first is being
seen in Saudi Arabia and an agreement has been made between the two
and we can look at that element, the
market for
passenger tickets, for Saudi Arabia
motor, it will be entitled to it under this, if we
look at it, then tomorrow, on the
first date of 30th December, the
General Sales Agreement ji is such a low ji such a low
general sales agreement which is India's
largest online
market and other services to have presence
in the Saudi
first and it has been made big here
They will get the base ready and its stock will be seen to have a
huge
impact.
Now the banks will take the services of
ICICI Loam for services insurance
and the general
insurance partner will be able to
insure all their children through birth
and the benefit of this is between the two, so there are
approximately 980 banks and which are
seen in approximately the states and two union territories, so the bank has a large
network, now this ICICI Loam is going to be available
and the general insurance will be available
through this company
and now the customers will
also see it working in the insurance sector, so
see, it is the
largest airport service aggregate,
please announce it, the study partner is going to get a
big benefit, the
judgment which was
going on in the court regarding FM, the
court has given it to them through clearing
and if we look at it, today the
double bench of the Wonder Kar High Court of
Delhi,
in the appeal report made by FMC Corporation, i.e. FMC Corporation, was rejected in the court.
Singapore
FM was against it and this Corporation
India had filed a
P in the record and the double bench of the court has
rejected it in this case
and its
net form is going to be received, so we can keep it in tomorrow's
session, the
news that was in today's main will be
cleared in it and if you liked the video then do
share and like it, you can get the bell icon and
select all as well and till then
hello, see you for free in the next video.